Hello, I'm Sakura Endo.
This is Sakura Endo.
I'm in Jimbocho.
And since I was in the neighborhood, I stopped by Kanda Myojin.
We'll start from Kanda Myojin.
Ta-da!
Can you see it? We started from such a nice gate...
I'd like to visit the shrine, get a red seal, and then tour around Jimbocho.
The reason I came to Jimbocho is to eat curry.
I like curry, so I thought Jimbocho is all about curry.
I want to go to a good curry shop and eat a lot of curry, so I'm going for a walk.
This time...
That's great!
I've been to Kanda Myojin before.
I have, but...
It's been a while, so I'm nervous.
I love shrines, so I'm happy.
Here we go!
All right!
Finished praying!
I'll get it from the master.
Excuse me, please.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Bye-bye!
There you go.
I got this.
This is a stick-on type, so I'm going to take good care of it when I get home.
Done! What's that?
Akari.
Please call me Akari.
I'm sure you can't hear me because my voice is so quiet.
Akari.
Akari with me
Where are you?
This one?
I'm over here.
Akari.
It's nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Yes.
It's so refreshing.
It's nice, isn't it?
It makes me feel like I'm doing my best.
It's been a while since I've filmed on YouTube by myself.
I don't know what to say.
What should I say?
Oh, you know, the drama.
It's set in Kanda Myojin, right?
I guess a lot of people come here to make pilgrimages to the holy place.
I don't know.
It's windy.
It's cold.
What shall we talk about alone?
It's nice to take a walk, isn't it?
I don't know, I don't have much to say.
It's nice to go for a walk, isn't it?
If I can walk home from work, I'll walk.
I don't go out on weekends.
I don't go out of the house on weekends, so if I don't walk, I'll become a person who doesn't move.
I'll become a person who doesn't move.
I try to take walks regularly.
Kijiri Bridge
I'm going to cross it.
This is the place where sparrows come out to lock their doors.
You can see the station.
Train
It's so beautiful.
It's big.
I knew Jimbocho was famous for curry, but never came here to eat.
I've been eating the commercial curry sold in supermarkets.
I've been eating store-bought curry all my life.
I really like Japanese curry.
So I'm sure that there are many curry shops like this one.
I'm sure that the curry shops in these places are full of spices and
I'm sure there are a lot of curry restaurants that I've never tasted before.
I'm very excited about it.
I think curry is a savior.
Even if I can't eat rice, I can definitely eat curry.
So curry is my savior.
I love it!
Thank you for everything!
I see it! I see it! I see the curry shop!
We have arrived at our destination!
Today we eat...
Ethiopia Curry and Rice Specialty Restaurant.
Ethiopia!
Can you see it?
I'm not very good at this.
I'm not good at this.
So this is it.
Look at that!
Yay!
Okay, let's get right into it.
I'm looking forward to it. Hello.
It smells so good.
It smells so good. I don't know what's good here.
There's so much to choose from. Vegetables, chicken, beef...
I can't decide. Wait a minute.
Chicken curry sounds delicious.
I'll have the chicken curry.
Chicken curry, please.
Do you have a table?
Yes.
I'd like you to choose a kalasa.
How would you like it?
We have colors from 0 to 70.
Okay, I'll take the middle color of 0, please.
Your choice of seat.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Choose your favorite seat.
Where do you want to sit?
Do you want to sit at the end?
There we go.
Stand up.
That's good.
Look at this.
It's a curry pin.
Everyone knows I like curry.
So my manager found this and bought it for me.
The manager found it and bought it for me.
Next time preview
I never thought I'd get to show it to everyone.
Can you put it on?
When you say "dip"...
Do you mean you're going to eat it with this?
Oh, you mean like this?
You're like a girl who really likes curry.
What should we do? Let's think about it.
All right, take off your jacket.
It was cold outside, so it's warm.
It's so cute.
Whoa!
Grandpa Takako gave it to me while jumping out of his skin.
How spicy is 70 times spicier?
Thank you very much.
We hold the gratitude of our customers in our arms.
Boom!
Can you see it?
It looks so good!
What do you mean?
Yes, sir.
Well, let's have some of this, shall we?
Oh, it's so hot.
Bon appétit!
It's so steamy.
Yum!
Yeah, it's good.
It's delicious.
What?
Oh, yum!
I like it medium hot.
Delicious!
It's so different from the Japanese curry I usually eat!
Yum!
I was a little hungry.
I'm going to be mute, okay?
Chicken.
My eyes.
Yum.
Oh, my God.
I can't stop eating it.
But they say curry is a drink.
Yum.
Potatoes.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Medium spicy.
Just right
I am satisfied!
Actually, we were going to go to another curry shop.
I had a delicious curry.
Actually, I'd like to go to another curry shop after the first one. Thank you very much for the curry.
I'm going to go to the next one, so I'm going to walk a little bit to empty my stomach a little bit and go to the next one.
There are so many used bookstores in Jimbocho that I never get tired of walking around!
There are so many used bookstores in Jimbocho, I never get tired of walking around!
I could spend a whole day in Jimbocho and never get bored!
I think we're already at the second bookstore.
And here we are!
Kitchen Nankai!
Ta-da!
I'm sorry to bother you.
Hello, I'm sorry to bother you.
Well, let's see...
There's a lot on the menu.
I'll have one curry and rice.
Curry with pork cutlet?
Curry with pork cutlet, please.
I'd like it.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
It's hot.
Look at that!
Curry with pork cutlet!
Looks delicious!
Shall we eat it right away?
Well, since we're here...
Put this on it.
Bon appétit!
Here we go.
It's a little difficult... a little difficult...
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Yummy, yummy, yummy.
Delicious!
Wow.
Yum.
Yuck!
I'm so skinny.
Let's have the pork cutlet then.
You just fried it right in front of me.
Yes!
Delicious.
Yum!
And enough spice.
Mmm... for everyone.
I'll feed and tuck in.
3 times, over 10 hours.
Wow, over 10 hours.
Oh, my God.
Yum.
Yummy.
Is it spicy?
If you keep eating it, it gets spicy.
But you can eat it.
After?
Later.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
The pork cutlet.
I was able to eat it crispy.
It was delicious!
After this, I think I'll go to the bookstore I've been wanting to go to.
I think I'll go there.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for the food!
Oh no, I'm so full!
I've walked for about three days.
You're walking with a very hunched back.
Oh, no, just a little bit.
Woah.
Wait a minute.
I'm too full to walk.
I really can't walk.
I'm in pain, I'm in pain, I'm in pain.
I'm in pain, I'm in pain, I'm in pain, I'm in pain.
All right. All right.
It's getting all dark.
I was hoping to go to the bookstore.
I'm trying to get there, but it's gonna be there soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is it.
Yes!
Nyanko-do.
This is Kitten House.
I wanted to come here because of the cats.
That's the main attraction.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Wow.
He's so cute.
Sleep tight.
Okay.
Well, I'll take your word for it. Take your time.
Wow, he's cute.
There's nothing but cats in here.
Really?
There's nothing but cats.
Nothing but cats.
Nothing but cats!
This picture book...
I love this book.
It's so cute!
Covered in cats
Eh, it's cute!
It's cute, but...
I'm surrounded by cats
Cute
Cute!
Cute.
I'm too cute
It's too cute
4 days mouth
Rest
here
3 days gone
Otte inho
can swim
I want to move
Thank you for watching.
Thank you
please.
Cute.
For $1,650.
Yes, please.
I'll take it.
I'll go put the cover on.
Thank you very much.
I'll take the cover, too.
It's cute.
Yes, I got it.
I'll take good care of it.
It's cold outside.
It's cold out, isn't it?
Be careful.
Thank you very much.
Yes, today I visited two curry shops and finally this Nyanko-do.
I also paid a visit to Kanda Myojin shrine.
It was a very fulfilling walk!
I've already done 5 steps!
I hope we can go somewhere again next time!
It was a lot of fun!
Thank you very much for taking a look.
See you soon.
Thank you for watching.